salisbury.edu 2019-04-17

# Privacy Notice | Salisbury University

  * Salisbury University X-26.00 Privacy Policy

At Salisbury University, we take data security and the privacy of your personal information very seriously.  We have updated our Privacy Statement and Policy to reflect the requirements of Maryland law as well as provide information to you about the European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), which went into effect in May 2018.  The policy provides you with information about what personal information we collect from you, how we collect it, what we do with it, and how your data is shared.  The policy also outlines your right to modify or remove personal information where applicable.

Salisbury University’s Privacy Statement and Policy apply exclusively to personally identifiable and confidential information collected by the University and to information that appears on the University’s websites.  Official University websites are defined as the web pages of the University, schools, departments, divisions or other units and any other sites specifically designated as official by the president, a vice president, dean, department head or director.  Official websites are generally recognizable by a standard template/layout carrying the University logo, contact information and reference to the University’s Privacy Statement. Please be advised that the University’s websites may contain links to other websites over which the University has no control.  The University is not responsible for the privacy and protection of any personally identifiable or confidential information on such sites.
